前情提要...
Previously on The Institute...
- 妈妈？
- 当然，孩子。随你心意。
- Mom?
- Sure, kid. Whatever you want.
欢迎来到研究所。
Welcome to the Institute.
你叫卢克·埃利斯。
来自明尼阿波利斯。
Your name's Luke Ellis.
You're from Minneapolis.
而且你很聪明。
And you're smart.
你是TK还是TP？
Are you TK or TP?
TP是心灵感应。TK是...
TP is telepathy. TK is...
念动力。
Telekinesis.
有时候东西会在我周围移动。
Well, sometimes things
move around me.
但这...这不足以...
But-but that
can't be enough to...
让你被带到这里？
To land you here?
我们现在在前区。
We're in Front Half right now.
- 还有后区吗？
- 是的。
- Is there a Back Half?
- Yeah.
等我们从前区毕业，就去的地方。
Where we go
when we graduate Front Half.
欢迎你，卢克。
Welcome, Luke.
你见过安保主管，斯塔克豪斯先生。
You've met Mr. Stackhouse,
Chief of Security.
这位是亨德里克斯博士。
And this is Dr. Hendricks.
他是这里尖端科技的总设计师。
He's the architect of the
cutting-edge science we do here.
我是西格斯比女士，
我是...
My name is Ms. Sigsby,
and I'm...
老大，我知道。
The boss, I know.
毫无疑问，
You are, without question,
你将参与拯救世界的行动。
about to participate
in saving the world.
等你服役期满，
And then, when you come
to the end of your service,
我们会清除记忆，送你回家。
we'll wipe your memory,
send you home.
我们不是怪物。
We're not monsters.
听着，小子，
Well, Son,
你完全大材小用来做这份工作。
you are ridiculously
overqualified for this job.
问题是，我们是个好团队。
Thing is, we're a good crew.
你只是个街头找来的路人。
You're just
some guy off the street.
人们总开玩笑说夜巡员没用，
People joke about
a night knocker,
但对小规模警力很关键。
but it's key for a force
as small as ours.
这世界上每天都在发生
There are things going on
every day in this world
你绝对难以置信的事。
that you would
not fucking believe.
你说得对。她确实不可靠。
You're right.
She was unreliable.
"确实"？
"Was"?
已经处理好了。
It's taken care of.
卢克，这是尼基。
Uh, Luke, meet Nicky.
想离开就自己想办法。
Yeah, we want out,
we get ourselves out.
那么，聪明小子，
So, Smart Kid,
我们该怎么离开这个鬼地方？
how do we get
the fuck out of here?
♪ 呐喊 呐喊 ♪
♪ Shout, shout ♪
♪ 尽情宣泄 ♪
♪ Let it all out ♪
♪ 这些都是我无法忍受的事 ♪
♪ These are the things
I can do without ♪
♪ 来吧 ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ 我在对你说话 ♪
♪ I'm talking to you ♪
♪ 来吧 ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ 在这动荡年代 ♪
♪ In violent times ♪
♪ 你不该出卖灵魂 ♪
♪ You shouldn't have
to sell your soul ♪
♪ 是非分明 ♪
♪ In black and white ♪
♪ 他们真的 真的应该明白 ♪
♪ They really,
really ought to know ♪
♪ 呐喊吧 呐喊 ♪
♪ Shout, shout ♪
♪ 尽情宣泄 ♪
♪ Let it all out ♪
♪ 这些都是我无法忍受的事 ♪
♪ These are the things
I can do without ♪
♪ 来吧 ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ 我在对你说话 ♪
♪ I'm talking to you ♪
♪ 来吧 ♪
♪ Come on ♪
顺便问下，你得过水痘吗？
By the way,
have you ever had chicken pox?
- 妈妈？
- 当然 孩子 随你心意
- Mom?
- Sure, kid. Whatever you want.
起床了 瞌睡虫！
派对开始了
Up and at 'em, sleepyhead!
Party's started.
你不想错过欢乐时光吧！
You don't wanna miss the fun!
♪ 前区再见 为你 ♪
♪ Goodbye Front Half for you ♪
♪ 前区再见 ♪
♪ Goodbye Front Half ♪
♪ 为你 ♪
♪ For you ♪
♪ 前区再见 ♪
♪ Goodbye Front Half ♪
♪ 亲爱的艾瑞丝 ♪
♪ Dear Iris ♪
♪ 前区再见 ♪
♪ Goodbye Front Half ♪
♪ 为你 ♪
♪ For you ♪
我是不是该许个愿，还是怎样？
Am I supposed to make
a wish or something?
随你高兴
If you'd like.
不如我许愿你能猜对我的年龄？
How about I wish you
got my age right?
这里只有13根蜡烛
There's only 13 candles.
哦 抱歉 亲爱的
Oh, sorry, honey.
这些代表你在前区度过的13天
These are for your 13 days in Front Half.
但现在你要启程了
But now you're on your way.
早上八点吃生日蛋糕？
Birthday cake
at eight in the morning?
「欢乐岛」记得吗？
"Pleasure Island," remember?
是啊 但这不代表
Yeah, but it doesn't mean
我想把糖霜当早餐好吗？
I want frosting
for breakfast, you know?
太他妈诡异了
It's fucking creepy.
嘿
Hey.
你今天要开始第一轮测试对吧？
You have your first day of tests today, right?
- 对
- 吃蛋糕 糖分有帮助
- Yeah.
- Eat the cake. Sugar helps.
- 帮什么？
- 信我就对了
- Helps what?
- Just trust me.
一切都会好起来的
Everything's gonna be all right.
所以 尼基...
So, Nicky...
尼基说你会想办法
帮他？
Nicky says you're gonna find
a way to help him?
会想办法帮我们所有人
Gonna find a way to help us all.
你就这么有把握？
You're that sure of yourself?
真让人羡慕
Must be nice.
艾瑞丝 时间到了
Iris, it's time.
她完全迷上他了
She's so into him.
知道吗 真好笑
她费尽心思
You know, it's funny.
She goes to all this trouble
想在心里对我隐瞒这件事 但...
to try and hide it from me
in her head, but...
我就想说「宝贝，你脸上都写着呢」
I'm like, "Babe,
I can see it on your face."
所以你们在一起了？
你和尼基？
So, you're together?
You and Nicky?
嗯 我...我不确定
Yeah, I-I wasn't sure.
看来我们半斤八两
I guess that makes the two of us.
说实话 我不知道
我和尼基算不算在一起
Truth is, I don't know
if Nicky and I are together.
我不知道我们是什么关系
I don't know what we are.
我是说 我认识他还不到两周 所以...
I mean, I haven't even
known him two weeks, so...
过几天见吧。
I guess I'll see you guys
in a few days.
- 好的。
- 行。
- Yeah.
- Okay.
嗯，回头见。
Yeah. See you soon.
天啊！
Jesus!
大日子啊，小老虎？
Big first day, huh, tiger?
你做好准备。
You get yourself ready.
我一两小时后回来接你。
I'll be back for you
in an hour or two.
走吧，艾瑞丝。
Come on, Iris.
"我们再也见不到她了。"
"We will see her no more."
- 早啊。
- 能搭把手吗？
- Hi. Morning.
- Hey, can you give me a hand?
- 呃，我正要...
- 帮个忙。
- Ah, well, I was...
- Please.
- 我本来...
- 太好了，麻烦你。
- I was, uh...
- Great, if you could.
- 我...
- 嗯。
- I was...
- Yeah.
...正要去拿...
...just about to grab...
- 好。
- 扶住她。
- Okay. Okay.
- Hold her, yeah.
- 出来了。
- 对...没错。
- There she is.
- That's a... yup.
- 是的。
- 没错。
- Yeah.
- Yup.
嘿。
Hey.
她喜欢你。
She likes you.
她单身。
She is single.
希望有警察住在附近
Hoping it'll give our regulars
some peace of mind having
能让老主顾们安心些。
a lawman living in their midst.
虽然可能会影响
Although it may cut back
on prom-night business
毕业舞会生意和本地孩子开房。
and local kids checking in
for weed and pillow fights.
是啊。
Yeah.
记得我们这位古利克森警官
Believe our friend，Officer Gullickson
几年前也是狂欢常客
used to be a part of those
revelries not so many years ago,
如果没记错的话。
if memory serves.
哦对了，她刚才来电
Oh, that reminds me.
She called a little bit ago
让你起床后
and asked me to have
you go down to the station
马上去趟警局。
as soon as you
were up and about.
那我该走了...
Well, I should probably go...
其实一开始
Actually, at first,
她想直接转接你房间
she wanted to be put
straight through to your room,
但你挂了勿扰牌。
but you had
the Do Not Disturb on.
我们斯坦顿酒店
And we at the Stanton Hotel
从不违背客人意愿。
pride ourselves on never
contravening our guests' wishes.
好，回见。
Okay, see you.
- 对吧贝蒂莉亚？
- 再见。
- Ain't that so, Bedelia?
- See you.
好了。
All right.
给你。
There you go.
甜蜜小家。
Home sweet home.
今早收到州警通报
We got a flash
from the Staties this morning.
有两个劫匪可能往这边来。
Two-man stick-up crew they think
might be headed this way.
一周前在新罕布什尔
They hit a convenience store
抢了便利店
down in New Hampshire
a week ago,
周一又在基特里作案
then a place in Kittery
Monday morning,
昨晚刚在班戈外围得手。
then last night
just outside Bangor.
要逃往边境？
Running for the border?
可能，除非他们往东走
Possible.
Unless they cut east,
1号路线应该
会把他们引到我们这边
Route 1 should
bring 'em right up our way.
明白
Got it.
所以你叫我来就为了警告我？
So, you called me
down here just to warn me?
电话里不能说吗？
Couldn't have done that
on the phone?
这就是大城市警校
That the kind of observation
教你的观察力？
they teach you to make
at big-city cop school?
警长让我问问，你要不要配枪
Chief told me to see if you
wanna be carrying a gun.
抓到人之前先用着
Just till we catch 'em.
保险柜里有几把备用格洛克
We got a couple of extra Glocks
in the safe.
这方面我自有准备
I'm all set on that front.
你有私人配枪？
You have your own weapon?
没有
I do not.
随你便
Suit yourself.
记住如果发生状况
And, obviously,
if anything goes down,
你唯一要做的就是上报
your only job is to call it in.
是 长官
Yes, ma'am.
有件事或许
你能帮上忙
There is one thing you might
be able to help me with.
这镇上哪儿能喝到
燕麦奶拿铁？
Where's a fella supposed to get
an oat milk latte in this town?
沃特维尔有家星巴克
There's a Starbucks
down in Waterville.
大概98英里远
It's about 98 miles.
不 这是大城市警察的玩笑
No, that was
a big-city cop joke.
我不喝拿铁
I don't drink lattes.
呼 那就好
听着...
Phew. That's a relief.
Look...
今晚务必小心
just be careful tonight.
要是那些混混真来了
Those punks
do roll through here,
粉笔可派不上用场
chalk's not gonna do much good.
也许吧 但别担心
Maybe. But don't worry.
他们斗不过我的机智魅力
They'll be no match
for my wit and charm.
想喝提神咖啡
You want some jet fuel,
去日出餐厅
往前两个路口右转
try the Sunrise Diner,
couple blocks down on the right.
谢谢 长官
Thank you, ma'am.
"长官"？
"Ma'am"?
女士？
Miss?
警官
Officer.
懂了
Got it.
她是绑架小组组长？
She was a snatch team leader?
是的 长官 去年刚晋升
Yes, sir. Promoted last year.
显然我们的审查程序
Obviously,
our vetting procedures
需要改进
need some improvement.
长官 正如西格斯比女士
和我讨论过的
Sir, as Ms. Sigsby
and I have discussed,
审查关键在于时间
vetting is all about time.
她多次向我强调
She's made me aware
on a number of occasions,
人员需求需要加快...
her staffing needs
require expediting...
不 我需要的是更多孩子
No. What I require is more kids.
作为绑架小组组长
And as a snatch team leader,
她知道全部行动细节？
she was privy to all aspects
of our mission?
不 长官 仅限前半区权限
No, sir. Front Half access only.
这并不能让人放心
That's hardly comforting.
你们跟踪她多久？
And you followed
this woman how long?
这是给您的
斯塔克豪斯先生
That's for you,
Mr. Stackhouse.
我们在三月份加强了被动监控措施。
We beefed up
passive surveillance in March.
上周已批准采取主动行动方案。
Active measures
were authorized last week.
"主动行动"是指...
你安插的记者？
"Active measures," meaning...
your reporter?
长官，我认为并非所有参会人员
都具备该权限...
Sir, I don't believe everyone on
this conference has clearance...
斯塔克豪斯先生，若我想让西格斯比女士回避
Mr. Stackhouse,
if I wanted Ms. Sigsby absent
这场谈话
她早就离开了
on this conversation,
she would be.
你确定那名叛徒
试图接触的对象
Now, you're confident your
reporter was the only person
只有你的记者吗？
that this traitor
tried to have contact with?
- 确定
- 那么西格斯比女士
- I am.
- Now, Ms. Sigsby,
我明白抓捕小组
I recognize that
the snatch team is not
不归你直接管辖
your direct responsibility.
但显然最有效的补缺方式
But obviously,
the most efficient way
是从你现有团队中
to fill this vacancy
抽调人手过去
is for you to move someone
over from your in-house staff.
你知道我们本来就人手不足
You... you know we're
undermanned as it is.
是的
Yes, I do.
但你也亲口说过
But you said so yourself.
随着新监控点的增加
With all the new keyholes
coming up,
真正需要的是更多孩子
what you really
need are more kids.
所以我真正需要的是
So what I really need
确保抓捕小组
全员待命
is for our snatch teams
to be at full strength.
现在我再问你一次
Now I'm going
to ask you once again
能否用更少资源
做更多事
to give me more... for less.
否则我只能向委员会
报告你...
Or I could simply tell
the Committee that you were...
无力完成既定目标数量
unable to handle the amount of
targets you've been assigned.
不不不 当然不是
我们都应各尽其责
No, no, no. No. Of course not.
We all have to do our part.
斯塔克豪斯先生的记者
怎么安排？
What about
Mr. Stackhouse's reporter?
想必已经过审查了吧
I presume she's been
through some vetting.
让她临时加入抓捕小组
What if she filled in
on the snatch team
直到找到正式替补如何？
until we had
a permanent replacement?
你觉得呢 斯塔克豪斯先生？
And how's that,
Mr. Stackhouse?
我会安排妥当
I'll make it so, sir.
很好
Very good.
所以你真策反了
一名记者？
So, you actually managed
to turn a reporter?
三年前安排她入职
I got her the job
three years ago
就是为了应对
这种状况
just for this kind
of eventuality.
还以为你会欣赏
我的深谋远虑
Thought you'd appreciate
my foresight.
确实欣赏
And I do.
但我不欣赏的是
What I don't appreciate
is you questioning
你在通话中质疑我的保密权限
my security status on that call.
放轻松 你知道他总对
权限问题小题大做
Easy. You know how worked up
he gets about clearances.
- 我只是给他个台阶下
- 却让我背黑锅
- I was just throwing him a bone.
- By throwing me under a bus.
真有意思
That's funny.
都忘了你这么幽默
I forgot how funny you could be.
没那么好笑
Not that funny.
你不会真以为我会
泄露机密吧？
You don't really think I'd
compromise this place, do you?
我知道你不会
I know you wouldn't.
这话还算中听
Well, that's
somewhat comforting.
哦 不是因为我信任你
Oh, not because I trust you.
而是因为你知道我清楚
But because I know that you know
要是这些事曝光了
that if ever
any of this comes out,
你也和我们一样完蛋。
you'd be just as screwed
as the rest of us.
你对今天的测试了解多少？
How much do you know
about what to expect today?
没想到你居然会在意。
Surprised you actually care.
我们是不是又得谈谈
Are we gonna have
to have another talk
让你好好配合的事？
about you being
a good cooperator?
听着 我知道你想测试我的TK基准值
Look, I know you're gonna try
to get a baseline of my TK.
省省时间吧 我无法主动触发能力
I'll save us both some time.
I can't do it on demand, okay?
只有受到刺激时才会显现
Only when something
activates it.
那我们就想办法刺激你咯？
Well, then we'll just have to
find a way to activate it, huh?
别总把"不行"挂嘴边 冠军先生
And let's take the "can't" out
of our vocabulary, huh, champ?
"不行"是弱者的口头禅
"Can't's a fucking beta word.
我是亨德里克斯医生
Ah, I'm Dr. Hendricks,
医疗部负责人
head of Medical Operations.
在西格斯比女士办公室见过
We met briefly
in Ms. Sigsby's office,
不过你当时状态不佳
but you weren't at your best.
卢克不喜欢握手
Oh, Luke doesn't shake.
没关系 完全没关系
That's all right,
perfectly all right.
但我说起跳时他会蹦起来
He does, however, hop up
in the chair when I say.
别又来你那套说教
Spare us another
teachable moment.
所以你真是医生？
So, you're, uh,
really a doctor, huh?
当然
Of course.
正经医学博士？不是心理专家那种？
But a medical doctor?
Not, like, Dr. Phil?
是的
Yes.
你们发的希波克拉底誓言呢？
What about all those oaths
they make you take?
"首先不伤害"原则呢？
"Primum non nocere"?
这和绑架未成年人
How does that square
with kidnapping
强制实验怎么自圆其说？
and testing without consent?
啊对 你是聪明那个
Oh, right.
You're the smart one.
不过你不是第一个
And yet, not the first
想用医德来难倒我的人
to think he can stump me
with Hippocrates.
我早就想清楚了
I assure you,
I've been all through
我们工作的道德边界
the morality
of the work we do here.
为了崇高目标可以不择手段
The ends more
than justify any means.
是吗？
Really?
- "拯救世界"是吧？
- 确实如此
- "Saving the world," right?
- As a matter of fact.
知道吗 "首先不伤害"
Hippocrates never
actually said it, you know?
根本不是希波克拉底说的
"Primum non nocere'?
拉丁语听着总是更高级
Everything just
sounds better in Latin.
- 显得更正式
- 不管是不是拉丁语
- It's more official.
- Latin or not,
希望你能明白这毫无意义
I hope you're smart enough
to realize it's meaningless.
"首先不伤害"
"First, do no harm."
所有手术都是伤害
All surgery is harm,
只是为更大利益服务的伤害
just harm in service
of a greater good.
- 别动
- 这是什么药？
- Hold still now.
- What's in that?
你关心这个干嘛？
What do you care?
要打进我胳膊里的
It's going in my arm, man.
没错 不管是什么都要打进去
That's right. It's going in,
whatever it is. Hmm?
现在别动
Now hold still.
你问药名无非是想
Only reason
you wanna know the name
这样你就能继续觉得自己比别人聪明。
is so you can go on
feeling smarter than everybody.
我想你的室友们跟你提过那些圆点的事吧？
I assume your bunkmates
have told you about the dots.
嗯？
Hmm?
提过一点。
Yeah, a little.
也说过发现它们时必须立即上报有多重要吧？
And how important it is
to tell us when you see them?
对，他们...他们跟我说了。
Yeah, they... they told me.
今天你不太可能看到那些圆点。
Very unlikely
you'll see them today.
今天是给你做基线测试的日子。
Today is about getting
your baselines.
你只需要放松坐着
All you gotta do
is sit back and relax
按照指示做就行。
and follow instructions.
嗯。
Hmm.
你必须知道！佐伊要你知道真相！
You need to know!
Zoe needs you to know the truth!
别再说她的名字！
Stop saying her name!
我只是想告诉你真相！
I'm just trying
to tell you the truth!
- 给我滚开！
- 佐伊！
- Get the hell out of my way!
- Zoe!
嘿，怎么回事？
Hey, hey, what's going on?
她疯了！她他妈就是个疯子！
She's crazy!
She's fucking crazy!
离我远点！
Stay away from me!
你不能再继续逃避了！
You can't keep
ignoring it anymore!
冷静，安妮。没事的。
Easy. Easy, Annie.
Everything's okay.
你怎么在这儿？
What are you doing here?
我正要去日出餐厅喝杯咖啡。
Well, I'm just on my way
to the Sunrise, grab a coffee.
吃早餐了吗？听说他们的煎蛋卷很棒。
You had breakfast yet?
I hear they make a mean omelet.
我得去警告她。
Huh, I've gotta warn her.
我知道。我知道，
I know.
I know, I know,
但你先得吃点东西。好吗？
but you gotta eat
something first. Okay?
这样吧，我请客。
Tell you what.
Tell you what, it's on me.
嗯？
Hmm?
我懂了。
I get it.
- 没事吧？
- 我需要...
- Everything all right?
- I need...
调度中心刚接到报警。
Dispatch just got a call.
斯隆太太？
Mrs. Sloane?
没事，一切都...都很好。
Yeah, yeah, everything's...
everything's fine.
都在掌控中，对吧？对吧？
All under control, right?
Right?
没人安全。没人能安全。
Nobody's safe.
Nobody is safe.
安妮，我知道警长已经厌倦讨论这事了。
Annie, I know Chief's
tired of going over this.
但你真的不能再骚扰斯隆夫妇了。
you cannot be bothering
the Sloanes anymore.
搞不好警长也是同谋。
Damn Chief could be in on it
for all I know.
- 天呐安妮。
- 你们可能都是同谋！
- For God's sake, Annie.
- You all could be in on it!
连我也是？
Even me?
这个...你刚来不久，所以...
Well, I...
You're new here, so...
但很快你就会知道真相。等着瞧吧！
But you'll learn the truth
soon enough. You'll see!
安妮，要不要来警局
Annie, you wanna come down
to the station,
和艾什沃斯警长谈谈？
talk to Chief Ashworth?
哦，我觉得没这个必要。
Oh, I don't think
we need to do that.
我和安妮正准备去吃早餐。
Annie and I were about
to go get some breakfast.
不用了，谢谢你们。
No, thank you, both of you.
我...我还有事要办。
I-I got errands to run.
好吧，只要你要办的事
All right, well,
as long as those errands
不包括去打扰可怜的斯隆太太。
don't involve going anywhere
near poor Mrs. Sloane.
小心他。
Careful with him.
他们长得和我们一样。
说话也像我们。
They look just like us.
Sound like us, too.
除了脚趾。
Except for the toes.
你得看小脚趾。
You gotta look
at the pinky toes.
它们...它们弯曲得很奇怪。
They're... they're
bent all funny.
哦！
Oh!
你以为自己是在做善事吗？
Suppose you think you're being
some kind of humanitarian?
和疯女人搞好关系？
Make nice with the crazy lady?
说实话，德鲁，我...
Tell you the truth,
Drew, I, uh...
我还没仔细想过。
I guess I hadn't
really thought about it.
好吧。既然现在开始想了，
Okay. Well, now that
we're thinking about it,
不如想想斯隆夫人的感受？
why don't we think about what
it's like for Mrs. Sloane?
失去孩子已经够惨了。
Bad enough she had
to bury a child.
现在还有你那个疯朋友
Now she's got your crazy friend
试图说服她这不是意外。
trying to convince her
it wasn't an accident.
你得给我解释清楚，伙计。
You're gonna have
to fill me in here, pal.
不，这不是我的工作。
No. Not my job.
你只要确保她远离凯莉·斯隆。
You just make sure she stays
away from Kelly Sloane.
我告诉你，
I'm telling you,
你们这是在自找失望。
You guys are setting yourself up
for disappointment.
这个不用你操心。尽力而为吧。
Let us worry about that.
Just try as hard as you can.
我真的在努力。
I'm really trying.
那就再加把劲，嗯？
Well, try harder. Hmm?
有进展吗？
Anything?
抱歉，我真的尽力了。
I'm sorry. I'm really trying.
我们这是在死马当活马医啊。
We're really scraping the bottom
of the barrel here, huh?
集中注意力，卢克。
Concentrate, Luke.
托尼，给他点鼓励。
Ah, Tony, give him a boost.
不，不要了，求你了。
No. No, no. No more, please.
我说过，今天不太可能看到光点。
Like I said, it's very unlikely
you'll see the lights today.
不过万一看到了，
On the off chance
you do, though,
你必须立刻告诉我们，
I need for you to let us know
immediately,
这是为你的安全着想。
for your own safety.
为我的安全...
For my safe...
还有，尽量咬紧牙关。
Also, do try to keep
your teeth clenched.
我可不想你咬断舌头。
I'd hate for you
to bite off your tongue.
好吧。
All right.
哈！我说过你能行的，冠军。
Huh! Told ya
you could do it, champ.
如果连你自己都不相信自己，
No one's gonna believe in you
别人更不会相信你。
if you don't
believe in yourself.
我...
I...
我觉得我要吐了。
I think I'm going to be sick.
让他坐这儿休息几分钟，
Okay, uh, let him sit here
a few minutes,
给他杯水，
give him a glass of water,
清理干净。
clean him up.
]
放松点，第一次都这样。
Easy. First time is rough.
给，这个能帮你。
Here, this'll help.
薄荷糖。
Spearmint.
看到光点了吗？
You see the dots yet?
没关系，你会的，
然后就会感觉好些。
That's okay. You will,
then you'll feel better.
说到这个，
Speaking of which,
你该吃点东西，
让胃舒服些。
you should eat something,
settle your stomach.
你看起来糟透了。
You look like shit.
谢谢。
Thank you.
我刚打了第一针点剂。
Had my first shots for dots.
跟我说说吧。
要知道，我第一次打针时，
Tell me about it.
You know, first time for me,
用牙咬住针头拔出来
I ripped the needle out
with my teeth
直接扎进了亨德里克斯的蛋蛋。
and jabbed it right
into Hendricks's balls.
真的假的？
Did you really?
假的。
Nah.
不过我想这么干，
现在还想。
I wanted to, though,
and I still may.
其实我吐在了新帆布鞋上。
Truth is, I barfed
all over my new Chucks.
小心点，乔治。
慢慢来。
Careful, George.
Just take it slow.
嘿！嘿！
Hey! Hey!
比起乔治刚经历的，
这都不算什么。
Guess it was nothing compared to
what George just went through.
那是什么？
What's that?
叫"梦境箱"。
It's called the "Dream Box."
是前区最后的测试。
It's the final test
in Front Half.
随时可能轮到我们。
Expecting it any day now.
知道是干什么的吗？
Any idea what it does?
据说是把你潜意识里
From what I'm told, it shows you
最糟糕的东西都挖出来。
all kinds of bad shit it dredges
up from your subconscious.
艾瑞斯管这叫
个人恐怖电影。
Iris calls it your
own personal horror movie.
只有对齐灯光
才能停止。
Only way to make it stop's
by lining up the lights.
证明你准备好
进入后区了。
Shows 'em you're
ready for Back Half.
能反抗吗？
Can you fight it?
呃，可以试试。
Well, I mean, you can try.
嘿，小情侣。
Hey, lovebirds.
最近看到光点了吗？
See any dots lately?
你脑子里全是光点吧。
You got dots for fucking brains.
随时奉陪，小子。
You and me, kid. Anytime.
嗯？
Hmm?
哦。
Oh.
抱歉。
I'm sorry.
你迟到了。
You're late.
是...对不起，我...
Yes, I-I-I'm sorry. I don't...
吃药了吗？
Did you take your pill?
- 你看不出来吗？
- 不想看。
- Can't you tell?
- I don't wanna look at it.
"化学让生活更美好"
"Better living
through chemistry."
给你。
There you go.
带跳绳了吗？
You have that jump rope?
能别说话吗？
Could you not talk?
收到。
Roger that.
别卖关子，
有办法出去吗？
Don't leave me in suspense.
Is there a way out of here?
听着，总有办法的。
Look, there's always a way.
这就像策略游戏。
It's pretty much
a strategy game.
难点在于想出
他们没防备的招，
The challenge is thinking
of a way they haven't
至少是他们觉得
我们不敢试的。
or, at least,
one they don't think we'd try.
好，洗耳恭听。
Okay, I'm all ears.
我们还没...
还没到那一步，明白吗？
We're not...
we're not there yet, okay?
我们还在收集数据。
We're still gathering data.
目前看到的监控摄像头
Now, the security cams I've seen
看起来像是十年前
最先进的型号。
look like they were maybe
state-of-the-art ten years ago.
每个公共区域都有一个
One in every communal room
每条走廊两端各一个
都是运动感应的。
and one on either side of every
hallway, all motion-activated.
估计连接了Wi-Fi网络
Guessing they're linked
into the Wi-Fi,
但应该还有有线备份。
but, you know, there's
probably a hardwire backup.
好，那我们
怎么破坏它们？
Okay, so,
how do we knock 'em out?
不知道。你手边有
Wi-Fi干扰器吗？
I don't know. Have you got maybe
a Wi-Fi jammer lying around?
或者四级激光笔之类的？
Or, I don't know,
a Class 4 laser pointer?
刚用完。
Fresh out.
我猜主服务器
锁得很严实。
My guess is that main server
is locked up tight.
所以我们没法破坏监控？
So, we can't knock them out?
有什么好笑的？
What's so funny?
托尼说"没法"是菜鸟用语。
Yeah, Tony says
"can't's" a beta word.
真他妈讨厌那家伙。
Fucking hate that guy.
还是解决不了摄像头问题。
Still doesn't get us
past the cameras.
最简单的办法
Well, the easiest way to do that
就是发展内应。
would be to recruit
an inside man.
内应？在这里？
An inside man? Here?
听着，所有组织
都有薄弱环节
Look, all organizations
have weak links. Okay?
人们都有不为人知的
怨恨和秘密。
People have secret resentments,
secret lives.
关于间谍招募
有很多好书可以参考。
There are a lot of good books
on spy recruitment.
M-I-C-E... MICE法则
M-I-C-E... MICE.
金钱、意识形态、胁迫、自负。
Money, Ideology, Coercion, Ego.
问题是我们只有一次机会
The only problem we have
is we only get one shot.
如果招募被拒绝
We recruit one of the staff,
get turned down,
对方会报告给
西格斯比或斯塔克豪斯。
and they report it
to Sigsby or Stackhouse.
是啊，没有第二次机会。
Yeah. No second chances.
而且时间紧迫。
Plus, we don't have
a lot of time.
卡丽莎说孩子们
Kalisha said
the average Front Half stay
在前区平均停留15天。
of any kid she's seen
is about 15 days.
我们需要的是
超强心灵感应者
What we really need
is a super powerful TP.
能读取工作人员思想
See inside the minds
of the staff,
包括他们隐藏的想法。
even the stuff they're hiding.
甚至能不知不觉
扰乱他们思维。
Maybe scramble their brains
without them realizing it.
连卡丽莎都没这么强。
Even Kalisha's
not strong enough for that.
而且等能力发展到那程度
Plus, by the time anyone
develops any real power,
就会被转移走了。
they get shipped out.
那是什么鬼东西？
What the fuck is that?
没人知道
每周都会出现。
Nobody knows.
It happens every week or so.
看起来不太环保。
Doesn't look very eco-friendly.
你怎么不去举报他们？
Yeah, why don't you report 'em?
德鲁告诉我
今天安妮的事。
Drew told me what happened
with Annie today.
听说你成功安抚了她。
Sounds like you
really calmed her down.
- 这可不简单
- 是啊
- That's not easy.
- Yeah, well, um,
我对这种事有点经验。
I have some experience
with that kinda thing.
- 是吗？
- 对
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
因为我妈妈。
Yeah, my mom.
抱歉。你父亲呢？
I'm sorry. What about your dad?
呃...
Oh, um...
他...他试着照顾过她一阵子
Yeah, he... he tried
to look after her for a bit.
但他离开后 她就开始停药了
But after he left,
she started going off her meds.
安抚她就成了我的工作
Basically became
my job to defuse her.
嗯
Hmm.
你肯定很擅长这个
I bet you were good at it.
她只是需要有人倾听
Well, she just needed
someone to listen to her.
她的妄想看似荒谬
Her delusions
might've seemed crazy,
但我总能发现其中有些真实成分
but I usually found there was
some grain of truth to 'em.
比如安妮和凯莉·斯隆的事？
Like Annie and Kelly Sloane?
什么意思？那不是意外？
What do you mean?
It wasn't an accident?
什么不是意外？
What wasn't an accident?
凯莉·斯隆女儿遭遇的事
Whatever happened
to Kelly Sloane's daughter.
那地方叫红台阶
Place is called the Red Steps.
- 嗯哼
- 其实不是台阶
- Mm-hmm.
- Not really steps,
只是河中央的岩石群
just a rock formation
in the middle of a river.
也不怎么红
Not really red either.
和土壤里的铁含量有关
Something about the iron content
in the soil.
总之我从小就被告诫
Anyway, all the time
I was growing up,
绝对不能在红台阶附近游泳
our parents told us never
swim near the Red Steps.
说那里的水流经过岩石时
Something about the way the
current gets around the rocks.
会把人卷下去
It can pull you under,
即使水面平静如镜
even when the surface
is calm as glass.
我们那儿也有类似的地方
We, uh,
we had a place like that.
废弃的花岗岩采石场
Abandoned granite quarry.
孩子们叫它'溺水机器'
Kids used to call it
'the drowning machine'.
我九年级时 几个毕业生在返校节前夜
When I was in ninth grade,
a few seniors went drinking
跑去红台阶喝酒
up at the Red Steps
night before homecoming.
可能是醉酒失足
Maybe they got tipsy
and fell in,
或是醉到真的想游泳
or maybe they got drunk enough,
总之四天后发现了尸体
they actually decided
to go for a swim.
两男两女
Either way, their bodies
washed up four days later.
其中一个女孩是佐伊·斯隆
Two boys, two girls.
凯莉的女儿
One of the girls was Zoe Sloane.
天啊
Kelly's daughter.
没想到安妮当时就在镇上
Jesus.
她不在
I didn't realize that
Annie was here back then.
她肯定是听说了这事
No, she wasn't.
然后坚信不是意外
She must've heard the story,
现在她脑子全乱了
convinced somehow
it wasn't an accident.
和其他阴谋论搅在一起
I don't know. It's all
messed up in her head now,
但这对凯莉·斯隆打击很大
combined with her
other conspiracy stuff,
我能想象
but it's been very upsetting
for Kelly Sloane.
安妮时好时坏
I can imagine.
有次她说...
Annie's got her
good days and bad.
她知道我母亲对我的昵称
Yeah. Yeah, something
she said... she, um...
安妮偶尔会说些惊人的话
She knew what
my mother used to call me.
她总能接收到些奇怪的频率
Yeah, Annie'll say some pretty
mind-bending shit time to time.
[翻译结果缺失]
She's tuned into
some strange frequencies.
嗯...我今晚过去一趟
Well... I'll go by tonight,
看看她情况怎么样
check on her,
see how she's doing.
你真是有心了
Well, that's good of you.
每个小镇都有这样的人吧
I guess every town's got one.
是啊
Yeah.
不 我不是那个意思...
No, I didn't mean...
没关系 都过去很久了
Oh, no, that's okay.
It was a long time ago.
谢谢你的咖啡
Thank you for the coffee.
你只剩最后一次机会了
You literally have
one guess left.
- P
- 不对
- P.
- No!
- 好吧
- 输了
- Okay.
- Dead.
你真菜
You suck.
重开一局 快点
Off the bat.
Start a new round. Come on.
等等 什么词来着
Okay. fuck.
Wait. What word?
快猜
Come on.
我正在想
I'm trying to think.
绝了
Amazing.
- 嘿兄弟
- 快看这个
- Hey, man.
- Hey. Check it out.
卧槽
Holy shit.
厉害啊
Impressive.
太牛了
Very impressive.
梦境舱很烂 但对我的TK能力帮助很大
Dream box sucks, but it's
done wonders for my TK.
这就是...它的用途吗
Is that the, uh...
is that the purpose?
强化TK能力
To amp the TK?
能强化所有能力
Amps everything.
感觉怎么样
How are you feeling?
像被人打成脑震荡
Like someone turned
my brain into a smoothie,
不过总体还行
but otherwise, all good.
你的TP能力呢
Mm. And how about your TP?
那些灯是你移动的吗
Did you, uh,
make those lights move?
应该是
I think so.
记不清了 你要买什么
I don't really remember.
What can I get for you?
呃...
Uh...
给我杏仁糖和维生素D3
Give me, uh, Almond Joy, D3.
还以为你会选椰子糖
Huh. I had you
for a Mounds kinda guy.
我总能给人惊喜
Well, you know,
I'm full of surprises.
- 谢谢
- 不客气
- Thank you.
- Any time.
- Y
- 对了
- Y.
- Yes! Yes!
偶尔也能蒙对
Sometimes it works.
元音字母嘛
It's a vowel.
不算太差 继续
Not that bad. Come on.
嗨
Hi.
嘿
Hey.
乔治好像好些了
Uh, George seems
a little better.
- 那就好
- 但维持不了多久
- Okay.
- Yeah, not for long.
如果他能移动梦境舱里的灯
If he was able to move those
lights in the dream box,
下次就轮到他进BH了
he's the next up for the BH.
你确定这不是好事
And you're 100% sure
that isn't a good thing?
又来了
Oh, here we go again.
听我说 别喝红色酷爱饮料
I'm telling you, Sha,
don't drink the red Kool-Aid.
在这里任何人告诉你的话
都是谎言。
Anything anyone tells you
in this place is a lie.
绝对的。
Period.
那莫琳呢？
What about Maureen?
少来这套。
Fucking spare me.
好吧，
来打乒乓球怎么样？
All right,
how about some ping-pong?
- 来吧。
- 好啊。
- Come on.
- Okay.
嗯，明白。
Uh, yeah, gotcha.
卢克，帮帮我。
Luke, help me out here.
我知道你不信
莫琳那套
I know you're not buying
Maureen's whole
随大流的说辞。
go-along-to-get-along spiel.
我不确定。
I don't know, man.
感觉她可能
是个真实的人。
Feels like there may be
a real person in there.
- 看见没？
- 是啊。
- See?
- Yeah.
如果莫琳是假的，
她为什么要告诉我们
If Maureen weren't for real,
then why would she tell us
所有摄像头
听不到的地方？
about all the spots where
the cameras can't hear us?
在我看来，艾瑞斯走了后，
现在唯一能信任的
Far as I'm concerned, with Iris
gone, the only people
就只有
这个房间里的人。
we can trust
are in this room right now.
再加一个。
Plus one more.
今晚会有
新孩子来。
They're getting
a new kid tonight.
他叫埃弗里·迪克森
来自盐湖城。
His name's Avery Dixon
from Salt Lake City.
他们会把他
安排进艾瑞斯的房间。
They're gonna put him
in Iris's room.
你准备对他施展
惯用伎俩吗，莎？
You gonna work your usual magic
on him, Sha?
滚开！
我真的得过水痘！
Fuck off!
I really had the chicken pox!
我不知道。
I don't know.
看这孩子的房间，
他可能
Judging by this kid's room,
looks like he may be
还太小不适合"魔法"。
a little young for "magic."
好了，你们两个
都别说了。
Okay, both of you need
to just drop this.
说真的，太荒谬了。
Seriously, this is ridiculous.
看我拿到了什么。
Look what I got.
哦，别这样。
Oh, come on.
不行！不行！
No! No!
也有我一份。
It's mine too.
- 我不能...
- 呃，乔治？
- I can't...
- Uh, George?
与其用它给你代币
去买汽水，
Instead of using it to give you
tokens to get the sodas,
为什么不直接用机器
why don't you use the machine
给你汽水
而不用代币呢？
to give you sodas
without tokens?
- 嘿，谁问你了？
- 随便说说。
- Hey, who asked you?
- Just sayin', man.
来场比赛吧。
伙计们，来吧。
Let's have a game.
Guys, come on.
我不需要你的。
我的更好。
I don't need yours.
Mine's better.
- 发球前对打。
- 好的。
- Rally for serve.
- All right.
打到十分，行吗？
To ten, okay?
- 开始吧。
- 想得美。
- Let's start.
- Yeah, in your dreams.
哦！
Oh!
嘿，你们...
奶油用完了！
Hey, you're, uh...
you're out of half-n-half!
能在柜台
留个便条吗？
Can you leave
a note on the counter?
哦，来，
我帮你写。
Oh, here,
let me help you with that.
先是可口可乐，
然后是健怡可乐，零度可乐，
First there was Coke,
then Diet Coke, then Coke Zero,
现在我还得订购
and now I have
to order something
叫零糖可乐的东西。
called Coke Zero Sugar.
啊，晚期
资本主义，对吧？
Aw, late-stage
capitalism, right?
其实并非如此。
Actually, it's not.
消费主义无法用任何经济模型预测。
Consumerism stands apart from
any predictive economic model.
好吧，你说得对。
Yeah. Yeah, okay, sure.
虽然凯恩斯学派会反对这种说法，
I know Keynes
would say otherwise,
但稍有常识的人都明白
but anyone with half a mind
knows it's production,
推动经济的是生产而非消费。
not consumption,
that drives an economy.
但你显然比'稍有常识'强得多。
But you clearly have
more than half a mind.
当时我在摩加迪沙国立大学
I was three years
into my economics doctorate
攻读经济学博士第三年。
at Jaamacadda University
in Mogadishu.
2007年，青年党开始追杀我的家人。
In 2007, Al-Shabaab
came after my family.
我们不得不逃离。
We had to leave.
抱歉，那段日子一定很难熬。
Sorry. That must have been hard.
在肯尼亚难民营的两年确实艰难。
Two years in a refugee camp
in Kenya was hard, yes.
但现在来到缅因州，
But here, now, in Maine,
就像是重获新生。感谢真主。
it's like a new beginning.
Praise Allah.
也祝福你和你的兄弟。
Praise to you
and your brother too, man.
以后你们的咖啡都算我的。
The coffee is on us
from here on out.
晚安。
Have a good night.
谢谢。
Thank you.
过来，姑娘，快过来。
Come on, girl. Come on.
哦，嘿。
Oh, hey.
看看哪个白痴把这家伙
Look what some dipshit
tossed in the dumpster
扔在拉森五金店后面的垃圾箱里。
out behind Larson's Hardware.
这是六角手风琴，别跟普通手风琴搞混了。
It's a concertina, so don't go
mistaking it for an accordion.
我...我不会弄错的。
Oh, I-I won't.
我有个姐姐以前...
One of my sisters used to...
...会弹一点。
...play a little.
反正不是我。
Clearly not me.
但她也不可能告诉你
But she wouldn't have
been able to tell you
那个研究所的真实内幕。
about that Institute,
what they really do up there.
你就待在这儿别动。
You stay right here.
安妮！待在原地！
Stay there, Annie!
警察！趴在地上！
Police! Get down on the ground!
快点伙计！我们走！
Come on, man! Let's go!
快上车！关门！
Hurry up! Get in!
Close the door!
有枪声！
Shots fired!
多比拉兄弟加油站发生交火！
Dobira Brothers' Gas Station!
至少一人中弹！
At least one down!
里面有便衣警察！
Uh, plainclothes
police officer inside!
多比拉先生，听得到吗？
Hey, hey, Mr. Dobira.
我是蒂姆。
It's Tim.
我是蒂姆，能听见吗？
Can you hear me, man?
我得帮你翻身，好吗？
I'm gonna have
to turn you over, okay?
-不要
-必须翻过来检查
- No.
- I've gotta turn ya.
-我知道很疼
-太疼了
- I know, I know, I know.
- It hurts.
我知道很疼，忍一忍
I know that it hurts, okay?
必须检查伤势
I've just got to take
a look at you, buddy.
保持呼吸
Breathe for me.
把手给我，用力按住伤口
Here, give me your hands.
Put pressure on that, okay?
用力压住，我在这陪着你
Pressure on it.
I got you, man.
明白吗？继续按住伤口。
Okay? Keep pressure on it.
我马上回来。
我很快就回来，好吗？
I'll be right back.
I will be right back, okay?
您这里有酒精吗，
多比拉先生？
You got any alcohol,
Mr. Dobira?
酒精？
Alcohol?
没有？
No?
我来了。我来了。
我就在这儿。
I'm coming. I'm coming.
I'm right here.
我在这儿。我在这儿。
I'm right here. I'm right here.
让我看看伤势。
把手移开。
Let's see what we've got.
Move your hands for me.
把手拿开。
好的。
Move your hands.
Okay.
呼吸，深呼吸。
好样的。坚持住。
Breathe, breathe, breathe.
That's my man. Okay.
开始处理伤口。
会没事的。
Let's get it in there.
It's gonna be okay.
会好起来的。
救援马上到。
It's gonna be okay.
Help is coming.
丹尼尔，又熬夜加班？
Daniel, burning
the midnight oil again?
嗯，准备明天的工作。
Uh, setting up for tomorrow.
我觉得再给艾尔斯先生
做一次梦境箱治疗就行。
I think we're one dream box
session away with Mr. Iles.
好消息。
Good news.
后续关键环节
都需要他参与。
We're gonna need him,
all the keyholes coming up.
我们会准备好的。
We'll be ready.
艾尔斯后面
还有几个对象...
Couple more
right behind Iles, so...
埃利斯那孩子怎么样？
What about the Ellis kid?
初步检测显示
他的TP值很低。
Well, his initial tests
indicate pretty low TP.
意料之中，
Not surprising,
毕竟BDNF水平一般，
但我们会让他达标的。
given his moderate BDNF levels,
but we'll get him there.
了解。
Good to know.
你应该也想到了，
Of course,
it must have occurred to you
即便是中等的
BDNF数值...
that even a moderate
BDNF score...
...配合埃利斯男孩
超群的智商，
...together with
the Ellis boy's superior IQ,
可能使他具有
独特价值。
might make him
uniquely valuable.
我的职责是激活
并提升他的TP值，
My job is to actuate
and invigorate his TP
直到能为蜂鸣计划
做出贡献。
to the point where he can
contribute to the Hum.
当然，丹尼尔。
这是我们共同的目标。
Of course, Daniel.
That's all our jobs.
但你也清楚，
某些情况下...
But you do know,
in certain cases,
受试者的真正价值...
可能远超预期...
our subject's true value...
an infinitely higher value...
另有他用。
might lie elsewhere.
呃...
Ah...
这个...
Uh...
别担心。
Don't worry.
这条走廊的麦克风
The microphones on this corridor
暂时故障了。
are experiencing
a temporary malfunction.
-斯塔克豪斯先生...
-叫我特雷弗就行。
- Mr. Stackhouse...
- Trevor, please.
特雷弗，我不知道
西格斯比跟你说了什么，
Trevor, look, I don't know
what Sigsby told you,
但我没有滥用职权
筛查PC患者。
but I'm not using
my position to scan for PCs.
这不仅超出了
我们目前的职责范围，
Not only is that outside
our mission purview now,
而且我很清楚
but I'm also very aware
有其他机构
专门负责此事。
that there are other
facilities so tasked.
说得好。
Well said.
完全是胡扯，
Complete bullshit,
不过说得漂亮。
but well said.
你说什么？
Excuse me?
没事的。别怕。
有我在呢。
It's okay. It's okay.
I got you, man.
我就在这儿。
I'm right here.
快点，快点。
Come on, come on.
快过来，快过来！
Come on, come on, come on.
举起手！让我看到你们的手！
Hands! I wanna see hands!
德鲁，我们需要叫救护车。
Drew, we need
an ambulance here, man.
- 德鲁，现在！
- 呃，什么...好吧，我们该...
- Drew, now!
- Uh, what... okay, what do we...
用你的对讲机。打给温蒂。
告诉她我们需要救护车。
Get on your radio. Call Wendy.
Tell her we need an ambulance.
腹部有枪伤。
Got a GSW to the stomach.
再让她发布全境通告
追查一辆吉普车，指南者型号，
And tell her we need an APB
on a Jeep, I think, um, Compass,
北卡罗来纳州车牌
前几位是WTB9。
North Carolina plate
starts with WTB9.
- 我只看到这些。
- 吉普车，呃...
- That's what I got.
- A Jeep, uh...
德鲁，叫救护车。
你能行的，兄弟。
Drew, ambulance, man.
You got this, bro.
呃-呃-呃，好的。温蒂，
Uh-Uh-Uh, yeah. Wendy,
我们需要派救护车
到多比拉家。
uh, we're gonna need an
ambulance to the Dobiras' place.
多比拉先生，呃...
Mr. Dobira, um...
已经在路上了...
15分钟到。
Already on the way...
15 minutes.
- 救护车在路上了。
- 全境通告。
- It's on the way.
- APB.
只有警长有权
发布全境通告。
Only Chief's supposed
to put out an APB.
就说是我他妈逼你发的。
Tell him I fucking forced you.
温蒂，我们还需要
发布全境通告...
Wendy, we're also
gonna need an APB...
你能搞定，对吧？
You've got this, okay?
...追查一辆新款
吉普指南者。
...on a late-model
Jeep Cher... Compass.
我不会离开的。深呼吸。
I'm not going
anywhere. Breathe.
呃，北卡车牌！
Uh, NC plate!
- 北卡车牌！
- WTB9开头，后面还有三位。
- NC plates!
- WTB9, then three more.
车牌是WTB9。
Plates are WTB9.
- 呃，颜色？
- 呃，深色。我想...
- Uh, color?
- Uh, dark. I think...
应该是黑色。车上两人
I think black. Both guys in it
都是20岁左右的白人男性，
都携带武器。
were late teens, early 20s,
white, both armed.
呃-呃，车辆颜色深，
Uh-uh, vehicle's dark,
两名男性嫌疑人，白人，
20多岁，持械...
two male suspects, white,
20-something, armed...
救护车快到了。
保存体力。
Ambulance is coming.
Save your strength.
爸爸。爸爸。
Dad. Dad.
爸，我们选法比安娜是因为
她专业能力过硬。
Dad, we chose Fabienne because
she knows what she's doing.
记得她的患者评分吗？
Remember her patient ratings?
是啊，在护理机构里
是最高的。
Yeah, the highest
of any aide with the agency.
不。不，我不觉得
她会藏你的眼镜。
No. No, I don't think
she's hiding your glasses.
好吧。
Okay.
谢谢。
Thank you.
什么？哦！
What? Oh!
今年这个班
实在太棒了。
I have such
a terrific class this year.
真的，我觉得三年级
是最适合教学的年龄段。
Yeah, I really think third grade
is my favorite age to teach.
因为... 他们心智发展
特别迅速，
Because... Yeah, their minds
are developing so fast,
你能产生很大影响。
and you can have so much impact.
我们刚读完《时间的皱纹》，
We're finishing
A Wrinkle in Time,
孩子们简直爱不释手。
which, of course,
they can't get enough of.
我在想下学期
And I thought, next semester,
可以试试《幻象天堂》。
we'd try The Phantom Tollbooth.
为什么不呢？
Well, why not?
我九岁时
你给我读过这本书。
You read it to me
when I was nine.
我怎么可能忘记呢？
Well, because how
could I forget?
哦，好吧。
Oh, okay.
好的。
Okay.
爱你。
Love you.
西格斯比的唯一任务
Sigsby's only directive
就是确保传送带持续运转
is to keep
the conveyor belt moving,
始终领先于关键节点。
stay ahead of the keyholes.
没错。
Right.
但还有另一种视角
But there's another perspective,
我想这正是你我共识
one, I think, you and I share,
这个视角着眼于
and that perspective takes in
那些具有真正PC潜质者
the almost incalculable value
无可估量的价值
of identifying individuals
识别这类人才意义重大
with genuine PC potential.
你我或许都认同这个大局观
You and I may share
that larger perspective.
但据西格斯比所说
But I understand from Sigsby
研究所集团并不认同
that the Institute Group
does not,
至少对我们的工作如此
at least as far
as the work we do.
她这话说得太他妈对了
She's sure as shit right
about that.
等等 你是说有第三方势力？
Wait. Are you saying
there's a third party?
不止一个第三方
Not a third party.
多股势力
Multiple.
他们都愿意砸下天文数字
All willing to funnel
astronomical sums of money
给任何能提供这种
to whoever can provide them
战略优势的人
with that kind
of competitive advantage.
那我该怎么做？
So... what do I do?
继续你现在的工作
Exactly what you've been doing...
发掘具有PC潜质的孩子
find a kid with potential
for PC development
然后培养他
and develop him.
你是指埃利斯？
Ellis, you mean?
这要由你来判断 博士
You tell me, Doc.
识别和培养是你的专长
Identifying and developing,
that's your department.
啊
Ah.
我只是提供工作空间
All I'm offering is room
for you to work.
还有买家
And a buyer.
西格斯比怎么办？
And what about Sigsby?
她怎么了？
What about her?
建议你管好枕边风
I'd say watch your pillow talk,
不过她应该不爱闲聊
but I can't imagine
she's much for talk.
明天见 医生
I'll see you tomorrow, Doctor.
-左边？
-好的
- Left side?
- Okay.
-这里
-准备好了？
- Here.
- Ready?
-好 二 三
-起
- Okay. Two, three.
- Up.
必须保护好现场
You need to keep
the scene secure
等班戈的鉴证组赶来
until the CSI team
gets here from Bangor.
预计他们很快会到
I'm supposed to get
an ETA shortly.
该死
Damn it.
多比拉先生没事吧？
Mr. Dobira gonna be okay?
急救员暂时稳住了伤势
EMTs have him stabilized
for now.
他至今运气不错 希望能保持
He's been awful lucky so far.
Let's hope it holds.
不只是运气好 长官
支援来得很快
Not just luck, sir.
Help arrived pretty quick.
干得好 德鲁
Nice job, Drew.
谢谢 警长
Thank you, Chief.
通缉令也发得很及时
With the APB, too.
消息传得够快
州警能在州际公路
Word got out quick enough,
the Staties could run roadblocks
双向设下路障
both ways on the interstate.
他们觉得已经把那帮混蛋逼入绝境了
They figured they've got
the assholes cornered.
我该去录口供了
好写报告
Well, I should, uh, tape up
so I can start my report.
你也是 蒂姆
Yours, too, Tim.
你得确保所有细节都准确无误
You wanna be sure you get
all the details right.
今晚还有几家要走访 头儿
Got a few more doors
to get to tonight, boss.
明早交报告行吗
Okay, if I give it to you
in the morning?
别忘了写上
Just don't forget
to include the part
你赤手空拳赶跑两个持枪劫匪那段
where you chased off two
armed robbers with no weapon.
- 谢了
- 不 你太棒了
- Thank you.
- Nah, you were great.
不 我表现很差
No, I wasn't.
但下次记得带尿布和凡士林 谁知道呢
But next time,
diapers and Vaseline. Who knew?
下次一定
Next time.
天啊 嘿
Jesus Christ. Hey.
嘿 别这样
Hey, hey, hey.
别哭 会没事的
Hey, don't cry.
It's gonna be okay.
我的天
Oh, my God.
- 嘿
- 没事的
- Hey.
- It's okay.
该死 能给他找条新裤子吗
Shit. Can we get him
some new pants?
- 我去拿
- 谢谢
- Yeah, I'll go.
- Thank you.
你会没事的
You're gonna be okay.
你是埃弗里对吧
从犹他州来的
Hey, you're Avery. Right?
You're from Utah?
我知道 会好起来的
一切都会好的
I know. It's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay.
- 要吃花生糖吗
- 不要
- You want a Reese's?
- No.
他过敏
He's allergic.
- 没事的
- 你怎么知道
- Hey, it's okay.
- How do you know that?
他告诉我的
He told me.
来 我们走
Okay, here we go. Come on.
- 没事了 没事了
- 谢谢
- You're okay. You're okay.
- Thank you.
好了
Oh, yeah.
给你
Here you go.
送你回房间吧
Let's get you back to your room.
那不是我的房间
It's not my room.
这个很强
This one's strong.
从没见过这么强的
I've never felt one so strong.
有...有多强
How... How strong?
这么说吧
Well, let's put it this way.
如果我的测试对象是大学替补球员水平
If my TP's a D-1 swingman,
这孩子简直就是他妈的乔丹再世
this kid's
Michael fucking Jordan.
有求必应
Ask and ye shall receive.